A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Third Administration, Subseries 37.3 FA439B
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Third Administration, 1967-1970; 3; 115 microform reels 115 microfilm reels.
  - Public Works (Reel 105, Reel 106)
    - Highways (Reel 105, Reel 106)
      - Richmond Parkway (Reel 106, Frame 23)
      - Route 17 (Reel 106, Frame 30)
      - Thruway (Reel 106, Frame 34)
      - Route 25A (Reel 106, Frame 37)
      - A-Z (Reel 106, Frame 47)
    - Specific Topics (Reel 106, Frame 87)
  - Resignations (Reel 106)
    - Agriculture & Markets (Reel 106, Frame 94)
    - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 106, Frame 96)
    - State Commerce (Reel 106, Frame 107)
    - State Correction (Reel 106, Frame 118)
    - County (Reel 106, Frame 121)
    - State Executive Department (Reel 106, Frame 130)
    - State Health (Reel 106, Frame 141)
    - State Labor (Reel 106, Frame 145)
    - State Mental Hygiene (Reel 106, Frame 150)
    - State Social Welfare (Reel 106, Frame 161)
    - State State University (Reel 106, Frame 167)
    - State Departments A-Z (Reel 106, Frame 181)
    - State Judiciary (Reel 106, Frame 188)
    - State Misc. (Reel 106, Frame 205)
  - Transportation (Reel 106, Reel 107, Reel 108, Reel 109, Reel 110, Reel 111, Reel 112)
    - Department of (Reel 106, Reel 107)
      - Aviation
        - Airports (Reel 106)
          - Jetports (Reel 106, Frame 210)
          - Dutchess County (Reel 106, Frame 219)
          - Kennedy (Reel 106, Frame 223)
          - Ramapo Valley Airport Spring Valley (Reel 106, Frame 234)
          - Westchester County (Reel 106, Frame 237)
          - General (Reel 106, Frame 239)
        - Aviation Fees (Reel 107, Frame 11)
        - General (Reel 107, Frame 21)
        - Hijacking (Reel 107, Frame 48)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 107, Frame 77)
      - Tristate Transportation Commission (Reel 107, Frame 81)
      - General (Reel 107, Frame 155)
    - Canals & Waterways (Reel 107)
      - Barge (Reel 107, Frame 220)
      - Erie (Reel 107, Frame 222)
      - Hudson River (Reel 107, Frame 223)
      - Neversink River (Reel 107, Frame 225)
      - St. Lawrence Seaway (Reel 107, Frame 229)
      - New York Harbor (Reel 107, Frame 236)
      - General (Reel 107, Frame 240)
    - Highways (Reel 107, Reel 108, Reel 109)
      - Aurora Expressway (Reel 107, Frame 253)
      - Clearview Expressway (Reel 107, Frame 255)
      - Hudson River Valley Expressway (Reel 108, Frame 13)
      - Jericho Turnpike (Reel 108, Frame 27)
      - Local Roads (Reel 108, Frame 34)
      - Long Island Sound Bridge (Reel 108, Frame 59)
      - Nassau Expressway (Reel 108, Frame 82)
      - Nu Way (Reel 108, Frame 88)
      - Richmond Parkway (Reel 108, Frame 97)
      - Sprainbrook Parkway (Reel 108, Frame 111)
      - Thruway (Reel 108, Frame 127)
      - Wantaugh Parkway (Reel 108, Frame 151)
      - Route (Reel 108, Reel 109)
        - 9 (Reel 108, Frame 153)
        - 9A (Reel 108, Frame 160)
        - 14A (Reel 108, Frame 164)
        - 25 (Reel 108, Frame 177)
        - 31 (Reel 108, Frame 181)
        - 87 (Reel 108, Frame 183)
        - 88 (Reel 108, Frame 187)
        - 9W - 15 (Reel 108, Frame 207)
        - 16-53 (Reel 108, Frame 214)
        - 54-99 (Reel 109, Frame 15)
        - A-Z (Reel 109, Frame 52)
      - General (Reel 109, Frame 105)
    - Railroads (Reel 109, Reel 110, Reel 111, Reel 112)
      - Long Island Railroad (LIRR) (Reel 109, Frame 139)
      - New Haven (Reel 110, Frame 14)
      - New York Central (Reel 110, Frame 27)
      - Penn Central Commutation Reports (Reel 110, Frame 41)
      - Penn Central (Reel 110, Frame 90)
      - A-Z (Reel 110, Frame 160)
      - General (Reel 110, Reel 111, Reel 112)
        - Full Crew Law (Reel 110, Frame 186)
        - General (Reel 110, Frame 188)
        - Bond Issue
          - 1967 November 16-1970 (Reel 110, Frame 208)
          - 1967 January-November 9 (Reel 111, Frame 11)
        - Bus (Reel 111, Frame 141)
        - Federal-Aid Highway Program (Reel 111, Frame 181)
        - Grade Crossing Elimination (Reel 111, Frame 188)
        - Signs (Reel 111, Frame 191)
        - Subway (Reel 111, Frame 196)
        - General
          - 1970 June-December (Reel 111, Frame 235)
          - 1967-1970 May (Reel 112, Frame 13)
  - Veterans (Reel 112)
    - Institutions (Reel 112, Frame 74)
    - Division of (Reel 112)
      - Curtailment of Counseling Services (Reel 112, Frame 83)
    - General (Reel 112, Frame 97)
  - Welfare (Reel 112, Reel 113, Reel 114)
    - Institutions (Reel 112)
      - Warwring Training School for Boys (Reel 112, Frame 123)
      - A-Z (Reel 112, Frame 126)
      - General (Reel 112, Frame 139)
    - Department of (Reel 112, Reel 113)
      - Board of Social Welfare (Reel 112, Frame 164)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 112, Frame 178)
      - Commission for Blind (Reel 112, Frame 180)
      - Foods Stamp Program (Reel 112, Frame 186)
      - Indian Affairs
        - 1970 (Reel 112, Frame 227)
        - 1967-1969 (Reel 113, Frame 13)
      - General (Reel 113, Frame 23)
    - General (Reel 113, Reel 114)
      - Liuni Adoption Case (Reel 113, Frame 52)
      - Arden House Conference (Reel 113, Frame 56)
      - Assistance Cases (Reel 113, Frame 146)
      - Day Care Centers (Reel 113, Frame 191)
      - Federal Program (Reel 113, Frame 212)
      - Roxane Felumero Pupils Case (Reel 113, Frame 254)
      - Residency (Reel 114, Frame 12)
      - General (Reel 114, Frame 16)
  - Youth (Reel 114, Reel 115)
    - Division of (Reel 114)
      - Youth American Medals For Bravery (Reel 114, Frame 108)
      - General (Reel 114, Frame 120)
    - General (Reel 114, Reel 115)
      - Clearinghouse (Reel 114, Frame 133)
      - Governor's Conference on Youth (Reel 114, Frame 156)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Reel 114, Frame 161)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps (Reel 114, Frame 168)
      - 1970 White House Conference (Reel 114, Frame 191)
      - General (Reel 114, Reel 115)
        - 1968-1970 (Reel 114, Frame 203)
        - 1967-1969 (Reel 115)